<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Copyright (C) 2014 The Android Open Source Project

     Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
     you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
     You may obtain a copy of the License at

          http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

     Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
     distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
     WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
     See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
     limitations under the License.
-->
<resources>
    <!-- Don't test these features on watches. -->
    <string-array name="disabled_tests">
        <item>com.android.cts.verifier.notifications.NotificationAttentionManagementVerifierActivity</item>
        <item>com.android.cts.verifier.notifications.NotificationListenerVerifierActivity</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="snsr_device_suspend_test_instr">Once you begin the test, disconnect USB, then
      perform a palm press to turn off display and put device into suspend mode. The screen will
      turn on and device will vibrate once all the tests are completed.
    </string>

    <string name="da_tapjacking_instructions">
        1. Launch the device admin add screen by pressing the button below.\n
        2. Wait for an overlaying transparent activity to show up obscuring the device admin details window.\n
        3. The button to activate the admin should be disabled and should not register any taps.\n
        4. Wait 10 seconds for the overlaying transparent activity to go away.\n
        5. Exit the device admin details and return to this screen.\n
        Pass the test if the device admin could not be activated while the details
        window was being obscured.
    </string>

    <string name="device_owner_network_logging_ui_info">
        1) Ensure the device has a lock screen enabled.\n
        2) Enable network logging by tapping on the left button below.\n
        3) View the lock screen by performing a palm press and then pressing a side button.\n
        4) Check that an icon appeared at the top of the lock screen. Tap the icon and unlock the device.\n
        5) Verify that a dialog about device monitoring opens, and informs you about: the name of the app that manages this device, details about the device owner\'s capabilities, and information that the admin can see the most recent network traffic log.\n
    </string>

    <string name="enterprise_privacy_quick_settings_info">
        1. Ensure the device has a lock screen enabled.\n
        2. Lock the device.\n
        3. Check that an icon appeared at the top of the lock screen. Tap the icon and unlock the device.\n
        4. Verify that a screen informing you what your managing organization can do is shown.\n
    </string>

    <string name="enterprise_privacy_keyguard_info">
        1) Press the Open Settings button to open Settings.\n
        2) Navigate to \"Personalization\" &gt; \"Screen lock\" and select the first screen lock type that is not \"None\".\n
        3) Use the Back button to return to this page.\n
        4) Lock the device.\n
        5) Verify that an info icon appeared at the top of the lock screen.\n
        6) Unlock the device.\n
        7) Repeat steps (1) through (6) for each screen lock type other than \"None\".
    </string>
</resources>
